{
    "id": "4330a3f8a91240e3b290c67bd32ad249",
    "title": "Simple Past Or Present Perfect Tense Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "She ………………….. English for the last 20 years.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "taught",
                "has taught",
                "teaches"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "She ………………… English at university before she became a fulltime writer.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "taught",
                "has taught"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "I ………………… every book written by Jane Austen.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "read",
                "have read"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "Who …………………. ‘Pride and Prejudice’?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "wrote",
                "has written",
                "had written"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "Peter …………………… .. a window last night.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "broke",
                "has broken"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "She ………………… all her childhood in Mexico.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "spent",
                "has spent",
                "had spent"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "I can’t walk because I ………………… .. my leg.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "broke",
                "have broken"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "Regularly every summer, Andrew ………………… . in love.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "had fallen",
                "fell",
                "has fallen"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "Who ………………….. you those marbles?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "gave",
                "has given"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "I’m sure we ………………….. before.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "met",
                "have met",
                "had met"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        }
    ]
}